

# **CONTACT:**



+48 884-960-930



konradbieniek@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/konrad-bieniek-73779b17a



https://github.com/Pan-be



Bielsko-Biała, Poland



https://pan-be.vercel.app

# **SKILLS:**

- Html
- · CSS
- · Java Script
- React
- Node.js
- .Git
- Wordpress
- npm
- PHP
- MySQL
- mongoDB
- Figma
- Canva
- Photoshop

### **SOFT SKILS:**

- SCRUM
- Creativity
- Aesthetic sense
- · Critical thinking
- Design knowledge
- · Skills for problem solving

# **LANGUAGES:**

- Polish mother tongue
- English B2
- German A2
- Spanish A1

# **EDUCATION:**

University of Economics in Katowice major: finance and accounting, 2009-2011

Technical School of Hotel Management and Tourism in Bielsko-Biała 2005-2009

# **Konrad Bieniek**

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

(REACT)

# **ABOUT ME:**

I am a self-taught programmer and passionate about internet technologies. My journey into web development started back in high school when I launched my first project - a static website written in HTML and CSS. As a young adult, I temporarily gave up my passions, thinking adulthood was not the time for hobbies. Today, as a mature individual, I want to follow a path that interests me and work not just to pay the bills but also for personal development and satisfaction. That's why three years ago, I began studying front-end intensively, and today, as a junior front-end developer, I support myself and my family doing what brings me great joy.

In my private life, besides internet technologies, I am passionate about photography (especially aerial shots taken with a drone), engaging in sports such as calisthenics, and playing soccer with my sons. I also like to occasionally take a break from the technology-filled world by going camping in the forest.

#### PROJECTS:

	( ICOSECIOI		
•	Portfolio (Next.js, React)	live   github	
•	newsletter sign-up application (Express):	live   github	
•	Expense Tracker (React):	live   github	
•	Simple Goals list (React)	live   github	
•	Hangman game (JS)	live   github	
•	Wallet with two color themes (JS)	live   github	
•	CV webpage (HTML+CSS)	live   github	

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

Hires SP. Z O.O.

Junior front-end developer, September 2023 - currently

In the position of a junior front-end developer, I am responsible for preparing views of landing pages and websites based on designs in Figma, updating changes in content, preparing configuration files, and implementing projects. I mainly use Tailwind, HTML, and JS. Older projects also require me to have knowledge of Bootstrap.

**LUCRUM GAMES SP. Z O.O.** 

Sales representative, website administrator (WordPress), March 2022 - currently

in addition to customer service and acquiring new ones, I administer and manage the website. I have improved the complaint system by creating a simple form, and at the moment I am working on an application for creating orders by customers. The technology I will be using in it is react, and at a later stage I plan to connect it to a database (probably firebase).

•

## **GOLDBERG&SONS**

Telephone Customer Service->Customer Advisor->Team Leader, 2010-2016

I'd be happy to tell more about my experience.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).